<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lines on Hugo Site of ycmega</title>
    <link>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lines on Hugo Site of ycmega</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fake Ascention</title>
      <link>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/fake-ascention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/fake-ascention/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;your-article-content-here&#34;&gt;Your article content here&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;$\Sigma_{i=1}^n{if(x_i)}$&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;【Warning: Object source unknown, please report to the database】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Warning: Infection level exceeded critical threshold [severe]】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【An unknown error has occurred. Please reconnect】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Warning: Protocol re-signing restriction&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Protocol re-signing restriction lifted: Externally lifted by [unknown source]】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Protocol re-signing successful&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Directory updating&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【M.I.N.D Beacon deployed, target linked and ready&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Link successful, object: LUNA [unknown source]】&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Do you know what forms the fundamental foundation of the Commander-Constructor tactic?&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This seems to be a tactical command lesson from a distant past, when I was called back by the teacher upon leaving the classroom. How did I answer this question back then?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;M.I.N.D Beacon.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;No&amp;hellip;It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;rsquo;trust&amp;rsquo;. The commander holds the life and death of the constructors, while the state of the constructors’ M.I.N.D also constantly influences the commander. However, because of this, the constructors must trust the commander&amp;rsquo;s commands, and the commander needs to have trust in the combat capabilities of the constructors. When you lead your team into battle, issue combat signals, and give attack orders, the constructors wholeheartedly believe in you. They will carry out every one of your instructions. Although it may not be suitable on the battlefield, —it&amp;rsquo;s beautiful, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? Only absolute trust can truly bridge the gap between the commander and the constructors. It&amp;rsquo;s such a simple truth, but many graduates&amp;hellip; eventually forget it. Commander 08299, I hope you&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haruki smiled</title>
      <link>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/sagrada-reset-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/sagrada-reset-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;一&#34;&gt;一&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;惠与春埼离开校舍后，便在校园角落的一张长椅上坐下。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;下午三点的夏日天空，带着淡淡的浅蓝色。位置愈高便愈接近蓝色，愈低便愈接近白色，呈现漂亮的层次。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;棒球社在操场上练习。惠眺望着那样的场景，开口问道：&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「春埼有什么想法？」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;关于冈绘里的事情，两人已经大致打听过一遍了。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;春埼回答：&#xA;「她想变得跟惠一样这点，有点令人在意。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;还有对冈绘里而言，坏人就是指强者。虽然过程极端，但惠也想到了原因。惠以前曾经跟她聊过那样的话题。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「惠不是坏人喔。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「这就难说了。而且，冈绘里说的是两年前的我。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「无论过去还是现在，你都没什么改变。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「那样也让我有点受到打击呢。我是自认为多少有变得正经一点。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;春埼轻轻微笑道：&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「你看起来一点都没有受到打击的样子喔，惠。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;那副笑容近似春埼美空平常的表情。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;真要说的话，就像是心情好时，内心深处的感情直接连接到表面般清爽的笑容。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;不过稍微有些不同。无论眉毛、脸颊、嘴角还是眼睛，全都有点僵硬。现在的她，只有表面在笑而已。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「你害怕冈绘里吗？」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;惠问道。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;春埼大概是害怕有可能会失去自己的能力。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;重启对春埼，以及对惠而言，都是意义极为重大的能力。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「我只有一个问题。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;春埼说道。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「惠，假设我的能力被冈绘里封印，变得无法使用重启，会对我跟你之间的关系造成什么变化吗？」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;少女的声音跟平常一样平淡。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;春埼美空的重启，以及浅井惠的记忆保持。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;只要一使用就会连自己的记忆都消除的能力，以及只能记住事物的能力。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;两人的能力若不一起使用就没有意义。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;这两个能力，将两人比什么都还要强烈地连接在一起。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;失去重启，就代表两人失去一起行动的理由。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;惠轻轻摇头。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「我不知道。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;残忍的回答。而且恐怕比惠所想象的还要残忍许多。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;春埼美空的语气没有变化。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;「那我绝对不会失去这个能力。绝对。」&lt;br&gt;&#xA;说完后，少女露出微笑。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;明明她可以直接生气，或是哭出来的。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;但春埼美空选择微笑。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
