<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gray Raven on Hugo Site of ycmega</title>
    <link>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/tags/gray-raven/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gray Raven on Hugo Site of ycmega</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/tags/gray-raven/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fake Ascention</title>
      <link>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/fake-ascention/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ycmega.github.io/hugo-blog/lines/fake-ascention/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;your-article-content-here&#34;&gt;Your article content here&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;$\Sigma_{i=1}^n{if(x_i)}$&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;【Warning: Object source unknown, please report to the database】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Warning: Infection level exceeded critical threshold [severe]】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【An unknown error has occurred. Please reconnect】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Warning: Protocol re-signing restriction&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Protocol re-signing restriction lifted: Externally lifted by [unknown source]】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Protocol re-signing successful&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Directory updating&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【M.I.N.D Beacon deployed, target linked and ready&amp;hellip;】&lt;br&gt;&#xA;【Link successful, object: LUNA [unknown source]】&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Do you know what forms the fundamental foundation of the Commander-Constructor tactic?&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This seems to be a tactical command lesson from a distant past, when I was called back by the teacher upon leaving the classroom. How did I answer this question back then?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;M.I.N.D Beacon.&amp;rdquo;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;No&amp;hellip;It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;rsquo;trust&amp;rsquo;. The commander holds the life and death of the constructors, while the state of the constructors’ M.I.N.D also constantly influences the commander. However, because of this, the constructors must trust the commander&amp;rsquo;s commands, and the commander needs to have trust in the combat capabilities of the constructors. When you lead your team into battle, issue combat signals, and give attack orders, the constructors wholeheartedly believe in you. They will carry out every one of your instructions. Although it may not be suitable on the battlefield, —it&amp;rsquo;s beautiful, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? Only absolute trust can truly bridge the gap between the commander and the constructors. It&amp;rsquo;s such a simple truth, but many graduates&amp;hellip; eventually forget it. Commander 08299, I hope you&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
